Guide to the Fund For Human Dignity records, 1974-1988
Fund For Human Dignity records, 1974-1988
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Fund for Human Dignity records, 1974-1988
7309
Fund for Human Dignity.
.6 cubic feet
Correspondence, minutes, memoranda, financial records and reports, publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, minutes, memoranda, financial records and reports, and publications; correspondence with the National Gay Task Force (NGTF).
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Fund for Human Dignity was a functional adjunct of the National Gay Task Force.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Fund for Human Dignity.
Subjects:
Gays.; Lesbians.; Gay liberation movement.; Homosexuality.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Organizational documents, administrative files, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Administrative files, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
- Educational materials (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NGTF, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Invitation to Benefit Dinner, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Administrative files, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8-11)
- NGTF 6th Annual Award Dinner and Benefit for F.F.H.D., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Administrative files: Anti-violence, AIDS, etc., 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Administrative file: Anti-violence, AIDS, Benefit Dinner, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Administrative files, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
- Administrative files:Anti-violence, etc., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Administrative files, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Administrative files, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- "The Fund at Ten", "The NGTF Fund for Human Dignity", 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Administrative files, planning documents, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- NGTF, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Administrative files, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Administrative files: LGBT History Class, etc., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Administrative files, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
- Administrative files: AIDS, etc., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Administrative files, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11-15)
- Administrative files, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- "News from NGTF" (press releases), 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- "NGTF AIDS Update", 1984, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Annual report, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Publications Removed From Collection 7309 - Cataloged As Serials In The Human Sexuality Collection:
Task Force Report, three issues.
Fund Focus, three issues.